(Sheldon:)So what?
I don't issue invitations to your mother.
(Missy:)It would be nice not to have to drive
to Anaheim in rush hour.
(Sheldon:)And don't ever call me Shelly.
(Leonard:)So it's settled. You'll stay with us.
(Howard:)I'll walk you to your car.
You're in Structure 3, Level C, right?
(Sheldon:)What just happened?
So anyway, we're 8 years old...
(Missy:)...and Sheldon converts my Easy-Bake Oven
to some kind of high-powered furnace.
That's just classic.
(Sheldon:)I needed a place to fire
ceramic semiconductor substrates...
(Sheldon:)...for homemade integrated circuits.
He was trying to build some sort of
armed robot to keep me out of his room.
(Sheldon:)Made necessary by her insistence
on going into my room.
Anyway, I make those little muffins
they give you. There's a big flash.
(Missy:)Next thing you know,
my eyebrows are gone.
(Howard:)Not your eyebrows?
(Missy:)Yep, I had to go through
the entire second grade...
(Missy:)...with crooked eyebrows
my mom drew on.